[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12_getoffbeach",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 1,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1201_0100_d_00_container_getoffbeach",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1201_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_getoffbeach",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "S_getoffbeach_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@title_getoffbeach",
        "Description": "@desc_getoffbeach",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@proposal_getoffbeach",
        "InProgressResponse": "@incomplete_getoffbeach",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@12_complete_available_response_getoffbeach",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1201_0101_culldrowned",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1201_0101_d_00_container_culldrowned",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1201_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_culldrowned",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_getoffbeach",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1201_0101_culldrowned_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1201_0101_culldrowned_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1201_0101_culldrowned_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1201_0101_culldrowned_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1201_0101_culldrowned_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1201_0101_culldrowned_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1201_0101_culldrowned_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1201_0102_campandtools",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 1,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1201_0102_d_00_container_campandtools",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1201_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_campandtools",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_culldrowned",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1201_0102_campandtools_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1201_0102_campandtools_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1201_0102_campandtools_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1201_0102_campandtools_proposal_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1201_0102_campandtools_proposal_next",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1201_0102_campandtools_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1201_0102_campandtools_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1201_0103_boarproblem",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 2,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1201_0103_d_00_container_boarproblem",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1201_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_boarproblem",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_campandtools",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1201_0103_boarproblem_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1201_0103_boarproblem_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1201_0103_boarproblem_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1201_0103_boarproblem_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1201_0103_boarproblem_incomplete",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1201_0103_boarproblem_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1201_0103_boarproblem_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1201_0104_xmarksthespot_p1",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1201_0104_d_00_container_xmarksthespot_p1",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1201_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_xmarksthespot_p1",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_culldrowned",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1201_0104_xmarksthespot_p1_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1201_0104_xmarksthespot_p1_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1201_0104_xmarksthespot_p1_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1201_0104_xmarksthespot_p1_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1201_0104_xmarksthespot_p1_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1201_0104_xmarksthespot_p1_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1201_0104_xmarksthespot_p1_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1201_0107_preciouscargo",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1201_0107_d_00_container_preciouscargo",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1201_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_preciouscargo",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_xmarksthespot_p1",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1201_0107_preciouscargo_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1201_0107_preciouscargo_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1201_0107_preciouscargo_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1201_0107_preciouscargo_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1201_0107_preciouscargo_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1201_0107_preciouscargo_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1201_0107_preciouscargo_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1201_0108_introtosettlement",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 3,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1201_0108_d_00_container_introtosettlement",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1204_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_introtosettlement",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_preciouscargo",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1201_0108_introtosettlement_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1201_0108_introtosettlement_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1201_0108_introtosettlement_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1201_0108_introtosettlement_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1201_0108_introtosettlement_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1201_0108_introtosettlement_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1201_0108_introtosettlement_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1225_0101_truffles",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 3,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1225_0101_d_00_container_truffles",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0425_HerbalistMB_Town",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_truffles",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1225_0101_truffles_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0425_0101_truffles_title",
        "Description": "@0425_0101_truffles_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0425_0101_truffles_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0425_0101_truffles_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0425_0101_truffles_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0425_0101_truffles_complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1204_0102_warnmagistrate",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 3,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1204_0102_d_00_container_warnmagistrate",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1202_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_warnmagistrate",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_introtosettlement",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1204_0102_warnmagistrate_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1204_0102_warnmagistrate_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1204_0102_warnmagistrate_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1204_0799_TheHermitMB_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1204_0799_TheHermitMB_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1204_0102_warnmagistrate_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1204_0102_warnmagistrate_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1206_0103_hearthwohome",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 3,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1206_0103_d_00_Container_hearthwohome",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1202_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_hearthhome",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_warnmagistrate",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1206_0103_hearthwohome_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1206_0103_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1206_0103_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1206_0103_a1_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1206_0103_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1206_0103_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1206_0103_f_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1202_0102_intrototrader",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 4,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1202_0102_d_00_container_ intrototrader",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1202_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_intrototrader",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_hearthhome",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1202_0102_intrototrader_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1202_0102_intrototrader_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1202_0102_intrototrader_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1202_0102_intrototrader_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1202_0102_intrototrader_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1202_0102_intrototrader_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1202_0102_intrototrader_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1203_0102_introtooverseer",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 4,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1203_0102_d_00_container_introtooverseer",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1204_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_introtooverseer",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_intrototrader",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1203_0102_introtooverseer_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1203_0102_introtooverseer_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1203_0102_introtooverseer_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1203_0102_introtooverseer_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1203_0102_introtooverseer_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1203_0102_introtooverseer_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1203_0102_introtooverseer_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1204_0101_overseersettlement",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 4,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1204_0101_d_00_container_overseersettlement",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1204_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_overseersettlement",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_introtooverseer",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1204_0101_overseersettlement_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1204_0101_overseersettlement_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1204_0101_overseersettlement_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1204_0101_overseersettlement_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1204_0101_overseersettlement_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1204_0101_overseersettlement_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1204_0101_overseersettlement_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1204_0103_introtoartificer",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 4,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1204_0103_d_00_container_introtoartificer",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1205_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_introtoartificer",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_overseersettlement",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1204_0103_introtoartificer_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1204_0103_introtoartificer_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1204_0103_introtoartificer_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1204_0103_introtoartificer_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1204_0103_introtoartificer_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1204_0103_introtoartificer_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1204_0103_introtoartificer_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1205_0101_craftforartificer",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1205_0101_d_00_container_craftforartificer",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1205_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_craftforartificer",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_introtoartificer",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1205_0101_craftforartificer_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1205_0101_craftforartificer_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1205_0101_craftforartificer_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1205_0101_craftforartificer_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1205_0101_craftforartificer_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1205_0101_craftforartificer_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1205_0101_craftforartificer_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1205_0102_campingunlock",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1205_0102_d_00_container_campingunlock",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1203_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_campingunlock",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_craftforartificer",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1205_0102_campingunlock_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1205_0102_campingunlock_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1205_0102_campingunlock_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1205_0102_campingunlock_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1205_0102_campingunlock_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1205_0102_campingunlock_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1205_0102_campingunlock_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1203_0201_survivalistquest",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1203_0201_d_00_container_survivalistquest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1203_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_magistratequest",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_campingunlock",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1203_0201_survivalistquest_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1202_0201_magistratequest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1202_0201_magistratequest_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1202_0201_magistratequest_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1202_0201_magistratequest_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1202_0201_magistratequest_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1202_0201_magistratequest_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseEventTags": "HFR"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1203_0201_survivalistquest_V2",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1203_0201_d_00_container_survivalistquest_V2",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1203_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_magistratequest",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_campingunlock",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1203_0201_survivalistquest_V2_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1202_0201_magistratequest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1202_0201_magistratequest_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1202_0201_magistratequest_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1202_0201_magistratequest_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1202_0201_magistratequest_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1202_0201_magistratequest_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1203_0202_returntomagistrate",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 6,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1205_0102_d_00_container_returntomagistrate",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1202_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_returntomagistrate",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_magistratequest",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1203_0202_returntomagistrate_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1205_0102_returntomagistrate_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1205_0102_returntomagistrate_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1205_0102_returntomagistrate_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1205_0102_returntomagistrate_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1205_0102_returntomagistrate_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1205_0102_returntomagistrate_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1202_0202_introtoallfactions",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 6,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1202_0202_d_00_container_introtoallfactions",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_introtoallfactions",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_introtoallfactions_accepted",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1202_0202_introtoallfactions_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "1209_0103_timetochoose",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1202_0202_introtoallfactions_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1202_0202_introtoallfactions_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1202_0202_introtoallfactions_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1202_0202_introtoallfactions_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1202_0202_introtoallfactions_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1202_0202_introtoallfactions_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1207_0101_marauderquest1",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1207_0101_d_00_container_marauderquest1",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1207_Commander",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_marauderquest1",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_timetochoose",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1207_0101_marauderquest1_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9812_M_0001_RankUp",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1207_0101_marauderquest1_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1207_0101_marauderquest1_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1207_0101_marauderquest1_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1207_0101_marauderquest1_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1207_0101_marauderquest1_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1207_0101_marauderquest1_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1208_0101_syndicatequest1",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1208_0101_d_00_container_syndicatequest1",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1208_Alchemist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_syndicatequest1",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_timetochoose",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1208_0101_syndicatequest1_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9812_S_0001_RankUp",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1208_0101_syndicatequest1_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1208_0101_syndicatequest1_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1208_0101_syndicatequest1_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1208_0101_syndicatequest1_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1208_0101_syndicatequest1_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1208_0101_syndicatequest1_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1209_0101_covenantquest1",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1209_0101_d_00_container_covenantquest1",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1209_Adjudicator",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_covenantquest1",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_timetochoose",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1209_0101_covenantquest1_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9812_C_0001_RankUp",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1209_0101_covenantquest1_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1209_0101_covenantquest1_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1209_0101_covenantquest1_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1209_0101_covenantquest1_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1209_0101_covenantquest1_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1209_0101_covenantquest1_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1209_0103_timetochoose",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 6,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1209_0103_d_00_container_timetochoose",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_timetochoose",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_introtoallfactions",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1209_0103_timetochoose_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1209_0103_timetochoose_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1209_0103_timetochoose_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1209_0103_timetochoose_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1209_0103_timetochoose_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1209_0103_timetochoose_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1202_0403_factionhandoff",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1202_0403_d_00_container_factionhandoff",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1202_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_factionhandoff",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1202_0403_factionhandoff_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "1204_0501_encroachingcorruption",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1202_0403_factionhandoff_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1202_0403_factionhandoff_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1202_0403_factionhandoff_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1202_0403_factionhandoff_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1202_0403_factionhandoff_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1204_0501_encroachingcorruption",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 10,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1204_0501_d_00_container_encroachingcorruption",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1204_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_encroachingcorruption",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_factionhandoff",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1204_0501_encroachingcorruption_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "1204_0799_TheHermitMB",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1204_0501_encroachingcorruption_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1204_0501_encroachingcorruption_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1204_0501_encroachingcorruption_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1204_0501_encroachingcorruption_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1204_0501_encroachingcorruption_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1204_0501_encroachingcorruption_complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1205_0302_indigestion",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1205_0302_d_00_container_indigestion",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1202_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "12_Quest_02",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1205_0302_indigestion_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1205_0302_indigestion_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1205_0302_indigestion_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1205_0302_indigestion_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1205_0302_indigestion_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1205_0302_indigestion_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1205_0302_indigestion_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "MonarchsBluffsArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1204_0301_topplinggiants",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1204_0301_d_00_Container_topplinggiants",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1204_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "12_Quest_11",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1204_0301_TopplingGiants_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1204_0301_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1204_0301_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1204_0301_a1_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1204_0301_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1204_0301_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1204_0301_f_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1210_0101_devilhoney",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1210_0101_d_00_container_devilhoney",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1210_Barkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "12_Quest_07",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1210_0101_devilhoney_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1210_0101_devilhoney_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1210_0101_devilhoney_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1210_0101_devilhoney_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1210_0101_devilhoney_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1210_0101_devilhoney_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1210_0101_devilhoney_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "MonarchsBluffsArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1210_0201_daggermist",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1210_0201_d_00_Container_daggermist",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1210_Barkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "12_Quest_12",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_encroachingcorruption",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1210_0201_daggermist_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1210_0201_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1210_0201_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1210_0201_a1_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1210_0201_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1210_0201_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1210_0201_f_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "MonarchsBluffsArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1205_0301_broken_weapons",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1205_0301_d_00_container_broken_weapons",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1205_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "12_Quest_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_encroachingcorruption",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1205_0301_broken_weapons_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1205_0301_broken_weapons_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1205_0301_broken_weapons_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1205_0301_broken_weapons_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1205_0301_broken_weapons_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1205_0301_broken_weapons_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1205_0301_broken_weapons_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "MonarchsBluffsArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1203_0401_fashion",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1203_0401_d_00_container_fashion",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0403_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "12_Quest_06",
        "RequiredLevel": 15,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1203_0401_fashion_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1203_0401_fashion_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1203_0401_fashion_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1203_0401_fashion_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1203_0401_fashion_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1203_0401_fashion_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1203_0401_fashion_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "MonarchsBluffsArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1205_0501_ancientcraft",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1205_0501_d_00_Container_ancientcraft",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1205_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "12_Quest_13",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12_Quest_12",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1205_0501_ancientcraft_Success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1205_0501_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1205_0501_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1205_0501_a1_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1205_0501_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1205_0501_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1205_0501_f_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "MonarchsBluffsArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1203_0301_failed_harvest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1203_0301_d_00_container_failed_harvest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1210_Barkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "12_Quest_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12_Quest_13",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1203_0301_failed_harvest_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1203_0301_failed_harvest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1203_0301_failed_harvest_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1203_0301_failed_harvest_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1203_0301_failed_harvest_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1203_0301_failed_harvest_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1203_0301_failed_harvest_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "MonarchsBluffsArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1203_0302_root_problem",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1203_0302_d_00_container_root_problem",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1204_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "12_Quest_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12_Quest_13",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1203_0302_root_problem_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1203_0302_root_problem_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1203_0302_root_problem_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1203_0302_root_problem_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1203_0302_root_problem_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1203_0302_root_problem_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1203_0302_root_problem_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "MonarchsBluffsArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1204_0201_goodwill",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1204_0201_d_00_container_goodwill",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0610_Barkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "12_Quest_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12_Quest_04",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1204_0201_goodwill_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1204_0201_goodwill_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1204_0201_goodwill_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1204_0201_goodwill_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1204_0201_goodwill_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1204_0201_goodwill_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1204_0201_goodwill_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "MonarchsBluffsArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1204_0202_stores",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1204_0202_d_00_container_stores",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1204_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "12_Quest_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12_Quest_03",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1204_0202_stores_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1204_0202_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1204_0202_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1204_0202_a1_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1204_0202_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1204_0202_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1204_0202_f_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "MonarchsBluffsArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1202_0501_rightofway",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1202_0501_d_00_container_rightofway",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0602_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "12_Quest_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12_Quest_05",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1202_0501_rightofway_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1202_0501_rightofway_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1202_0501_rightofway_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1202_0501_rightofway_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1202_0501_rightofway_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1202_0501_rightofway_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1202_0501_rightofway_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "MonarchsBluffsArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1205_0303_crownjewels",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1205_0303_d_00_container_crownjewels",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1204_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "12_Quest_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12_Quest_05",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1205_0303_crownjewels_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1205_0303_crownjewels_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1205_0303_crownjewels_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1205_0303_crownjewels_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1205_0303_crownjewels_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1205_0303_crownjewels_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1205_0303_crownjewels_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "MonarchsBluffsArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1222_1501_intrototravel",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 12,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1222_1501_d_00_container_intrototravel",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0922_Innkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_intrototravel",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1222_1501_intrototravel_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "1222_1502_returntravel",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1222_1501_intrototravel_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1222_1501_intrototravel_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1222_1501_intrototravel_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1222_1501_intrototravel_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1222_1501_intrototravel_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1222_1501_intrototravel_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1222_1502_returntravel",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 12,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1222_1502_d_00_container_returntravel",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1222_Innkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_returntravel",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1222_1502_returntravel_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1222_1502_returntravel_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1222_1502_returntravel_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1222_1502_returntravel_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1222_1502_returntravel_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1222_1502_returntravel_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1204_0799_TheHermitMB",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 12,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1204_0799_container_TheHermitMB",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9901_MSQ_Yonas",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "MSQ_00_Init",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_MSQ_TheHermit_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1204_0799_TheHermitMB_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1204_0799_TheHermitMB_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1204_0799_TheHermitMB_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1204_0799_TheHermitMB_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@NPC_DefaultDialogue_1204_02_Overseer",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_9901_TheHermit_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_12_PVP_Area3_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_12_PVP_Area3_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_12_PVP_PoachArea_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_12_PVP_PoachArea_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_12_PVP_SpySpot_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_12_PVP_SpySpot_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_12_PVP_Area1_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_12_PVP_Area1_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_12_PVP_PoachArea_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_12_PVP_PoachArea_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_12_PVP_SpySpot_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_12_PVP_SpySpot_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_12_PVP_Area2_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_12_PVP_Area2_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_12_PVP_PoachArea_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_12_PVP_PoachArea_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_12_PVP_SpySpot_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_12_PVP_SpySpot_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1201_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1201_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1202_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1202_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1203_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1203_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1204_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1204_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1205_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1205_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1206_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1206_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1207_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1207_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1208_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1208_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1209_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1209_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1210_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1210_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1201_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1201_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1202_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1202_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1203_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1203_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1204_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1204_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1205_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1205_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1206_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1206_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1207_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1207_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1208_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1208_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1209_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1209_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1210_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1210_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1201_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1201_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1202_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1202_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1203_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1203_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1204_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1204_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1205_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1205_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1206_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1206_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1207_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1207_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1208_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1208_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1209_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1209_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1210_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1210_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1261_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1261_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1262_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1262_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1263_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1263_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1264_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1264_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1265_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1265_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1266_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1266_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1267_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1267_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1268_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1268_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1269_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1269_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1270_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1270_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1261_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1261_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1262_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1262_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1263_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1263_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1264_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1264_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1265_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1265_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1266_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1266_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1267_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1267_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1268_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1268_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1269_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1269_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1270_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1270_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1261_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1261_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1262_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1262_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1263_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1263_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1264_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1264_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1265_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1265_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1266_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1266_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1267_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1267_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1268_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1268_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1269_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1269_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1270_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1270_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_12_H_01_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_12_H_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_12_H_02_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_12_H_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_12_H_03_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_12_H_03_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    }
]